Othniel Charles Marsh Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1854-1899; Series II
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0653., 1884; 000999
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0705., 1884; 001051
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0757., 1884; 001103
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0795., 1884; 001141
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0842., 1884; 001188
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0871., 1884; 001217
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0882., 1884; 001228
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1010., 1884; 001356
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1044., 1884; 001390
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1069., 1884; 001415
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1099., 1884; 001445
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1102., 1884; 001448
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1124., 1884; 001470
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1141., 1884; 001487
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1154., 1884; 001500
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1223., 1884; 001569
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1234., 1884; 001580
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1276., 1884; 001622
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1338., 1884; 001684
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1340., 1884; 001686
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1467., 1884; 001813
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1477., 1884; 001823
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1511., 1884; 001857
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1514., 1884; 001860
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1530., 1884; 001876
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1549., 1884; 001895
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1568., 1884; 001914
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1668., 1884; 002014
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0445., 1885; 000791
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0507., 1885; 000853
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0522., 1885; 000868
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0595., 1885; 000941
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0671., 1885; 001017
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0736., 1885; 001082
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0770., 1885; 001116
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0785., 1885; 001131
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0872., 1885; 001218
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0937., 1885; 001283
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0953., 1885; 001299
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1011., 1885; 001357
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1055., 1885; 001401
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1060., 1885; 001406
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1120., 1885; 001466
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1126., 1885; 001472
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1143., 1885; 001489
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1211., 1885; 001557
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1300., 1885; 001646
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1513., 1885; 001859
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1516., 1885; 001862
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1536., 1885; 001882
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1566., 1885; 001912
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1678., 1885; 002024
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0429., 1886; 000775
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0431., 1886; 000777
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0437., 1886; 000783
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0544., 1886; 000890
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0545., 1886; 000891
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0579., 1886; 000925
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0812., 1886; 001158
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0912., 1886; 001258
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0913., 1886; 001259
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0935., 1886; 001281
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0947., 1886; 001293
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0993., 1886; 001339
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1086., 1886; 001432
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1087., 1886; 001433
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1122., 1886; 001468
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1180., 1886; 001526
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1197., 1886; 001543
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1258., 1886; 001604
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1303., 1886; 001649
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1333., 1886; 001679
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1350., 1886; 001696
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1364., 1886; 001710
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1373., 1886; 001719
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1499., 1886; 001845
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1502., 1886; 001848
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1613., 1886; 001959
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1621., 1886; 001967
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1649., 1886; 001995
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0428., 1887; 000774
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0470., 1887; 000816
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0550., 1887; 000896
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0601., 1887; 000947
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0607., 1887; 000953
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0720., 1887; 001066
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0780; [Is this Filhol?]., 1887; 001126
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0781., 1887; 001127
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0788., 1887; 001134
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1028., 1887; 001374
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1053., 1887; 001399
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1080., 1887; 001426
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1157., 1887; 001503
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1212., 1887; 001558
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1252., 1887; 001598
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1288., 1887; 001634
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1298., 1887; 001644
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1332., 1887; 001678
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1384., 1887; 001730
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1417., 1887; 001763
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1455., 1887; 001801
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1494., 1887; 001840
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1548., 1887; 001894
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1552., 1887; 001898
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1601., 1887; 001947
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1647., 1887; 001993
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1726., 1887; 002072
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0407., 1888; 000753
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0439., 1888; 000785
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0531., 1888; 000877
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0599., 1888; 000945
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0603., 1888; 000949
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0668., 1888; 001014
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0762., 1888; 001108
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0831., 1888; 001177
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0948., 1888; 001294
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0998., 1888; 001344
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1078., 1888; 001424
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1182., 1888; 001528
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1284., 1888; 001630
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1304., 1888; 001650
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1309., 1888; 001655
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1328., 1888; 001674
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1342., 1888; 001688
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1365., 1888; 001711
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1369., 1888; 001715
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1406., 1888; 001752
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1562., 1888; 001908
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1573., 1888; 001919
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1638., 1888; 001984
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0366., 1889; 000712
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0400., 1889; 000746
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0413., 1889; 000759
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0451., 1889; 000797
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0484., 1889; 000830
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0556., 1889; 000902
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0583., 1889; 000929
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0652., 1889; 000998
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0676., 1889; 001022
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0700., 1889; 001046
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0701., 1889; 001047
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0727., 1889; 001073
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0768., 1889; 001114
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0858., 1889; 001204
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0860., 1889; 001206
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0983., 1889; 001329
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1159., 1889; 001505
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1231., 1889; 001577
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1232., 1889; 001578
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1283., 1889; 001629
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1290., 1889; 001636
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1393., 1889; 001739
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1426., 1889; 001772
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1435., 1889; 001781
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1510., 1889; 001856
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1561., 1889; 001907
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1685., 1889; 002031
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0464., 1890; 000810
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0480., 1890; 000826
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0528., 1890; 000874
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0549., 1890; 000895
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0642., 1890; 000988
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0644., 1890; 000990
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0688., 1890; 001034
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0805., 1890; 001151
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0827., 1890; 001173
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0848., 1890; 001194
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1003., 1890; 001349
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1016., 1890; 001362
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1077., 1890; 001423
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1090., 1890; 001436
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1106., 1890; 001452
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1113., 1890; 001459
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1136., 1890; 001482
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1184., 1890; 001530
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1185., 1890; 001531
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1187., 1890; 001533
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1259., 1890; 001605